Guide to the Reginald R. Isaacs papers, 1917-1988, [bulk 1946-1988]
Isaacs, Reginald R. papers
- Series II. Professional work, 1917-1988
  - Walter Gropius Constructions, Plans, Projects 1906-1969, 1972-07 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Revista del instituto de cultura puertoriquena, 1961-07-1961-09 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Report - Slum Areas, Legal Aspects, 1936-04-14 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Unknown Items sent to Mark Isaacs, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Newspaper and Congressional Record, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - John H. Aldes Material, 1960-12-23 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Virgin Islands Planning Board Budget Estimates, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Virgin Islands Governmental Executive Orders and Memoranda, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Program for Community Improvement, 1962-02-01 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - State of the Territory Message of Governor Ralph M. Paiewonsky, 1968-01-22 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - A Handbook for Planning Board Members, 1971-07 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Virgin Islands Planning Board Biennial Report, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Charlotte Amalie Parking Study, 1974-07 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Chistiansted Parking Study, 1974-07 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Developing a Comprehensive Plan for the US Virgin Islands: VI200, 1974-05 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - US Virgin Islands Housing Market Study, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - The Feasibility of Medium-Rise Housing on Selected Sites, 1974-05 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - The Islands, 1968-01 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Master Plan for the Island of Saint Thomas and Charlotte Amalie, 1958-01 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Climate, Water Balance, and Climate Change in the North-West Virgin Islands, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Schematic Development Plan Estate Nazareth Virgin Islands, 1968-01-24 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Butler Hospital, 1963-02-25 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Propuesta para la planeacion ecologica del area metropeana del aburra, 1973-10 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Bases para la planeacion y desarollo del parque nacional "Las Orquideas", 1973-01 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - The Mystic, Charles and Neponset Rivers, Undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Proposed Park US Virgin Islands, 1970-09 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Gropius Book German Draft, Undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Title Pages, Outline, Foreword Volume 1, Undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Title Pages, Outline, Foreword Volume 2, Undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Appendices Volume 1, Undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Appendices Volume 2, Undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Materials (Not Sorted) Volume 2, Undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Publications Since 1964 (Bibliography), Undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Survey, Undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Misc. News Clippings Gropius Book, Undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Gropius Correspondence and Varia, 1949-1965 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Annual Summary of Programs and Activities Virgin Islands, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Walter H. Blucher Correspondence, 1957-1965 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Walter H. Blucher Correspondence, 1977-1983 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Cornell University Olin Library Correspondence, 1981-10-09 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Appendices to the Preliminary Report on the Conservation of Middle-Aged Neighborhoods and Properties, 1944-10-16 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Citizen Participation, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Walter H. Blucher Letters, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Walter H. Blucher Correspondence Photocopies, 1959-1965 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - The Neighborhood Theory Manuscript and Notes, 1947-1959 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Fort Hunt Case, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Walter H. Blucher Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - The Neighborhood Theory, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - America Can't Have Housing, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Municipal Conservation Authorities Act Drafts, 1952-07-20-1953-01 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Printed Material, Cards and Postcards, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Homestead Agency Material 1 of 2, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Homestead Agency Material 2 of 2, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Homesteading 1 of 2, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Homesteading 2 of 2, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Lucas Metropolitan Housing Authority, 1984-09-25 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Misc. Material, Undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Virgin Islands - Maps Sewage Systems, Undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Monthly Planners, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Monthly Planners, 1982-1984 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Virgin Islands Planning Board Annual Report, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Estate Profit - Comprehensive Plan, Virgin Islands, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Rebuilding Britain, 1943-02 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Report of CIAM 10, Dubrovnik, 1956-08 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Lecture by Walter Gropius, "Rebuilding Our Communities" Signed, 1945-02-23 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Report of President's Advisory Committee on Government Housing Policies and Programs, 1953-12 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - New Republic, 1947 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - The Nation, 1933-1944 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Harvard Publications, 1972-1986 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Urbe, 1962 -1970 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Designing Environments for the Aging, 1977-08 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Landscape Architecture, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - A Development Proposal Adjacent to Michael Reese Hospital, 1952-04-16 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Internal affairs at the Harvard Graduate School of Design, 1965-1975 (Box 15)
  - Internal affairs at the Harvard Graduate School of Design, 1965-1975 (Box 16)
- Series III. Personal and other family items, 1935-1987
  - Articles by Isaacs' father on Marcel Breuer, Le Corbusier, Josef Albers, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Alvin Simon Civil Engineering Scholarship Material Isaacs Memorial, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Reginald Isaacs Obituary and Gropius Manuscript, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Charlotte Isaacs Retirement Documents, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Mark Isaacs Landscape Documents, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - WH Blucher Material and Correspondence with Mark Isaacs, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Mark Isaacs' Draft Planning Book, Undated (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Mark Isaacs Military Draft Material, 1968-06-1968-11 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Mark Isaacs Military Draft Material, 1967-1971 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Mark Isaacs Military Draft Material, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Mark Isaacs Military Draft Material, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Mark Isaacs Military Draft Material, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Mark Isaacs Military Draft Material, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence with Grand-daughters, 1986-06-22 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - "Tunnel" Short Story by Charles Isaacs, Undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Kenneth S. Isaacs Papers, 1965-1985 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Charlotte Isaacs Trust, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Charlotte Isaacs Hoffman Lab Consultant, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Charlotte Isaacs items, Undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Isaacs Memorial, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Misc. Documents, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Misc. Personal Documents, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Charlotte Isaacs Retirement Photos and Newsclip, 1979-05 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Misc. Personal Documents, 1970-1986 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Misc. Personal Correspondence and Documents, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Personal Documents, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Prof. Isaacs' Cardiologist Correspondence, 1986-04 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, 1980-1985 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Portrait of Isaacs, Undated (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Certificates, 1935-1979 (Box 17)
  - Certificates, 1941-1950 (Folder 1)